Marcos Henrique Dogo

Experience in the IT area a little more than 1 year, performing capture of text using REGEX (Regular Expression) and development of report and component development. I'm not currently last semester of the Systems Analysis and Development course by the UNIFATECIE EAD University Center. I currently work as a self-employed person with deliveries and a driver (UBER).

Custódia Street. 225 Santo André, SP, 09240-140

+55 11 93753-2984

marcoshdogo@outlook.com
linkedin.com/in/marcoshdogo-2608/
https://github.com/MarkinhosHD

OBJETIVE

Trainee in JAVA programming

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Grifon Brasil Assessoria Ltda. EPP. São Paulo — *Administrative Assistant.*

MARCH 2016 - JULY 2016

 Working with Text Capture from the Official Gazettes of all over Brazil, using Regular Expression;

Grifon Brasil Assessoria Ltda. EPP. São Paulo — Intern

OCTOBER 2015 - MARCH 2016

• Performing Text Capture using Regular Expression;

Mahler Tecnologia em Internet LTDA – EPP. São Paulo — Intern

SEPTEMBER 2014 - MARCH 2015

- Parameterization of the Gr5 System.
- Report Development.
- Component Development Language used "PostgreSQL".

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND:

UniFatecie University Center — Analysis and Systems Development

START IN JANUARY 2021 - END IN JULY 2023

Studying the last semester of Systems Analysis and Development online.

HARD SKILLS

Back End Training — *Jdev Treinamentos Online*

JAVA OOP - Beginning on 01/25/2022 and completed on 08/26/2022

GIT/GITHUB Trainind — Dev Superior (YouTube Nélio Alves)

Versioning Basic Course - Complete.

SQL Server 2019 — *Alura Ensino Online*

 $3\ training\ courses$ - Beginning on 08/27/2022 in progress.

- SQL SERVER SGBD
- RELATIONAL DATABASE MODELING Conceptual, Logical and Physical

Formação Front End — B7WEB

5 training courses - Beginning on 08/27/2022 in progress.

- HTML5
- CSS3